So I was just Okay, guys. So I was just
reading the book. Then the doorbell
ringed suddenly and then I woke up and
then ran through the area and then I got
the package right now. Then I opened it
and I did not know how to cut it. So I
needed my dad's help. And anyways, there
I just opened it
and it was a pretty long time because I
do not know how to open because the tape
was literally odd. It's so hard.
And then I finally opened it and I
thought the blue the blue part was the
candy, but it was not actually the
candy. It was the box that was the that
the candy was inside. and I show you the
logo of it right now.
Okay, I'm just showing you. Okay, that's
the logo of it. And it says I see I see
a logot. My dad works in that company.
And that's the full logo if you want to
see.
And that over there,
the logo again.
And then skip that box by shaking the
floor.
And now throw the box.
And I did not know how to open this. And
I finally opened it. And then I saw this
happy birthday card because before
before that a few days before that
package was sent it was my dad's
birthday
and it says happy birthday to you.
So I'm reading the card. It says happy
birthday because on 7th of July it's my
father's birthday and on 4th of July is
my favorite and happy birthday to you.
Hope the birthday celebrations with your
with family was amazing. Sending you and
your family warm wishes. Hope your days
are filled with joy and a year filled
with success.
And there's nothing.
This is five stars. bring this Indian
chocolate brand every Indian chocolate
brand here if you are American
and why this why is this chocolate
okay so this is very good and this is
also very good but another version of it
and it's my favorite version
and this one I like this one and these
two
and this one I nuts and then uh these
are just like M&M's but
I say hello but all the bosses it's
really my dad and thank you for all of
this for making my dad's birthday
special
and fun fact
my school actually has ICIC mobile cards
on everyone's birthday I will give you
one also it's in my school kit
and box on it right now. And there's a
my old bag on it.
And
this is five star.
I said that so many times I cannot. And
gems the copy of Dominance. And bye
guys. Make sure to like and subscribe.
I'm I'm liking I'm liking your company
guys.